<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Getting Ripped</string>

    <string name="pose1">       Step 1 : Begin by lying on your side, forearm down, knees slightly bent.\n\n
                                Step 2 : Roll slightly back onto your glute, like your sitting on the back pocket of your blue jeans and lift legs a few inches off the mat. Bring top hand behind the head so elbow is also bent.\n\n
                                Step 3 : Lift legs up bringing your knees to your elbow while at the same time crunching your elbow toward your knee. Squeeze your waistline with each lift. Perform desired number of reps and switch sides. \n\n


                                </string>

    <string name="pose2">       Step 1 : Lay down on your back on the exercising floor with your knees bent. Place your feet flat and widen then slightly more than  your shoulder-apart-width.
                                Step 2 : Starting position: Extend your arms towards the downward direction by the side of the body with your palms facing inwards.\n\n
                                Step 3 : While exhaling your breath, crunch your abs in the forward right direction. Try to catch your right ankle with the right extended arm (step 2). Stay there till the count of one.\n\n
                                Step 4 : Now while you’re inhaling your breath, leave the right ankle you caught hold of with your right arm and very slowly move back to the starting position.\n\n
                                Step 5 : Repeat the same for the left side.\n\n
                                </string>

    <string name="pose3">       Step 1: Lie on your back and extend your legs up to a 45-degree angle. Keep your arms straight and in line with the floor, palms facing down. Lift your head, neck and shoulders slightly off the ground.\n\n
                                Step 2: Keeping your legs stick straight and glued together with your toes pointed, start lowering one leg.\n\n
                                Step 3: Raise your lowered leg and lower the other, focusing on keeping your core engaged.\n\n
                                Step 4: Continue the movement, alternating between legs.\n\n

                                </string>

    <string name="pose4">       Step 1 : Sit on the ground with your legs extended out in front of you.\n\n
                                Step 2 : Place your hands on the ground beside you for support and lean back at a roughly 45 degree angle with your back straight.\n\n
                                Step 3 : Pull your belly button in towards your spine and raise your legs off the ground.\n\n
                                Step 4 : Contract your lower abs as you bend your knees and bring your legs towards your chest.\n\n
                                Step 5 : Squeeze your abs hard and slowly return to the starting position.\n\n

                                </string>

    <string name="pose5">       Step 1: Extend one leg from the hip so that your foot lifts off the mat a few inches.\n\n
                                Step 2: Your foot can point softly as it is released from the mat.\n\n
                                Step 3: As you extend your leg, your hip will lift slightly, but the challenge is to keep the rest of your body stable in plank position. \n\n
                                Step 4: This requires extra work from your abdominal, shoulders, and back.\n\n
                                Step 5 : Return your foot to the mat and extend the other leg.\n\n

                                </string>

    <string name="pose6">

                                </string>

    <string name="pose7">       Step 1: Begin by lying on your side, forearm down, knees slightly bent.\n\n
                                Step 2: Roll slightly back onto your glute, like your sitting on the back pocket of your blue jeans and lift legs a few inches off the mat. Bring top hand behind the head so elbow is also bent.\n\n
                                Step 3: Lift legs up bringing your knees to your elbow while at the same time crunching your elbow toward your knee. Squeeze your waistline with each lift. Perform desired number of reps and switch sides.\n\n\n\n

                                </string>


    <string name="pose8">       Step 1: Start seated with knees bent and feet flat on the floor, holding one dumbbell with both hands in front of the chest.\n\n
                                Step 2: Keeping the spine long and abdominals pulled in, lean slightly back and lift feet a few inches off the floor.\n\n
                                Step 3: If that is too difficult be sure to keep your feet down on the floor.\n\n
                                Step 4:Slowly twist the torso to the left and bring the dumbbell beside the left hip.\n\n
                                Step 5: Return to center, and then slowly twist to the right and bring the weight beside the right hip to complete one rotation. \n\n

                                </string>


    <string name="pose9">       Step 1: Lie on your back and lift your legs and arms up so they are extended toward the ceiling.\n\n
                                Step 2: Lift your upper back off the floor, reaching your hands toward your feet.\n\n
                                Step 3: Lower your legs toward the floor while reaching your arms overhead, keeping your shoulders off the mat and lower back pressed into the mat.\n\n
                                Step 4: Repeat the crunch motion to complete one rep.\n\n

                                </string>

    <string name="pose10">      Step 1: Lie on the bench, your butt, shoulders, and head should be flat on the bench with a slight, arch your back.\n\n
                                Step 2: Grasp the bar with your thumbs on the outside of a closed fist, using an overhand grip, with your arms slightly wider than shoulder-width apart.\n\n
                                Step 3: Remove the barbell from the rack and lock your elbows out before lowering the bar to your chest, at the nipple line.\n\n
                                Step 4: Take a deep breath and raise the bar above your chest with your arms extended, exhaling while you push upward\n\n
                                Step 5: Return the bar to just above your chest and repeat the exercise.\n\n


                                </string>

    <string name="pose11">      Step 1: Sit on an exercise bench with a dumbbell in each hand. Using a neutral grip, place and press the dumbbells together. \n\n
                                Step 2: Pull your shoulders down and back, and brace your abs.\n\n
                                Step 3: Lie flat on the bench and hold the dumbbells on your chest. Press the weights inward as hard as you can. Tuck your upper arms into your sides.\n\n
                                Step 4: Push the weights up and over your chest until your arms are straight but not locked. Keep the tension on your pecs by continuing to press the weights together.\n\n
                                Step 5: Lower the dumbbells to your chest and repeat.\n\n


                                </string>


    <string name="pose12">      Step 1: Sit on the bench and hold a dumbbell in each hand, with hands positioned at your shoulders, elbows bent and angled down below your ribs.\n\n
                                Step 2: Brace your core and press both dumbbells straight up over your chest as you exhale. Keep your wrists straight \n\n
                                Step 3: At the top of the movement, the dumbbells should almost touch each other and your arms should be perpendicular to the floor.\n\n
                                Step 4: Reverse the movement and slowly lower the dumbbells back to the top of your chest as you inhale.\n\n
                                Step 5: As you lower the dumbbells, your elbows should come down at roughly a 45-degree angle to your torso.\n\n


                                </string>


    <string name="pose13">      Step 1: Stand with your mid-foot under the barbell.\n\n
                                Step 2: Bend over and grab the bar with a shoulder-width grip\n\n
                                Step 3: Bend your knees until your shins touch the bar\n\n
                                Step 4: Lift your chest up and straighten your lower back\n\n
                                Step 5: Take a big breath, hold it, and stand up with the weight\n\n


                                </string>


    <string name="pose14">      Step 1: Stand perpendicularly next to a training bench and place a dumbbell next to it on the side you plan to row. \n\n
                                Step 2: Place your non-rowing hand and your same-side knee on the bench, with your other foot firmly planted on the ground.\n\n
                                Step 3: Do not row the weight with your shoulder. Your shoulders should remain relaxed.\n\n
                                Step 4: Squeeze your shoulder blades together and lead the row with your elbow.\n\n
                                Step 5: Once you have reached the top position, maximally contract the back muscles to increase muscle engagement.\n\n


                                </string>


    <string name="pose15">      Step 1: Grasp the bar with a wide grip with an overhand, knuckles-up grip. Other positions and grips are possible, but start with this standard position.\n\n
                                Step 2: Pull the bar down until it is approximately level with the chin. \n\n
                                Step 3: Exhale on the downward motion. While shifting just slightly backward is OK, aim to keep your upper torso stationary.\n\n
                                Step 4: Squeeze the shoulder blades together while maintaining square shoulders.\n\n
                                Step 5: From the bottom position, with the bar close to your chin, slowly return the bar to the starting position while controlling its gradual ascent.\n\n


                                </string>


    <string name="pose16">      Step 1: Stand on the ground with your feet hip-width apart.\n\n
                                Step 2: Place the barbell just above the shoulders on your trapezius muscles and hold them from both the sides.\n\n
                                Step 3: Bend the knees and lower into a squat. Go down till your knees are at 90-degree angles.\n\n
                                Step 4: Slowly stand up without locking the knees and repeat the move.\n\n



                                </string>


    <string name="pose17">      Step 1: Stand two feet away in front of a sturdy bench or chair, facing your back with your feet hip-distance apart. Hold a dumbbell in each hand.\n\n
                                Step 2: Put your left foot on the bench behind you (your thighs and shin should be perpendicular to each other). Make sure your right leg is straight.\n\n
                                Step 3: Bend your right knee, squeeze your glute, and lower your pelvis toward the ground. Go down until your right thigh is almost parallel to the floor and knee directly over your ankle.\n\n
                                Step 4: Pause for 2-3 seconds and then press your right heel into the ground to straighten your right knee to complete one repetition.\n\n



                                </string>


    <string name="pose18">      Step 1: Use an overhand grip to hold the bar at hip level.\n\n
                                Step 2: Draw your shoulders back and keep your spine straight.\n\n
                                Step 3: Push your hips back as you slowly lower the bar toward your feet.\n\n
                                Step 4: Press your hips forward to come into a standing position with the barbell in front of your thighs.\n\n


                                </string>

    <string name="pose19">      Step 1: Stand tall with your chest up and core braced, holding the barbell with your hands just outside of your hips, using an underhand grip.\n\n
                                Step 2: Keeping your chest up and your elbows tight to your sides, initiate the move by raising your hands slightly so you feel your biceps become engaged.\n\n
                                Step 3: While maintaining tension on your biceps, curl the bar up to shoulder height, then give your biceps a one-second squeeze.\n\n
                                Step 4: Start to lower the bar slowly, keeping your biceps tensed and engaged to work as many muscle fibres as possible.\n\n
                                Step 5: Once the bar is back in the start position, straighten your arms fully to tense your triceps to ensure that your biceps are worked through the fullest possible range of motion.\n\n


                                </string>

    <string name="pose20">      Step 1: Grab a pair of dumbbells and stand with your feet hip-width apart and a slight bend in your knees.\n\n
                                Step 2: Raise the dumbbells overhead, and lower them behind your head so that your hands are near your shoulders and your elbows are elevated.\n\n
                                Step 3: Maintain a neutral head and neck position. Your chin should remain tucked throughout the movement, as if you were holding an egg under your chin.\n\n
                                Step 4: Evenly distribute your weight and grip the floor with your feet to create a stable position. Pre-tension your shoulders and hips while engaging your core. \n\n
                                Step 5: While maintaining your alignment, squeeze your triceps to begin straightening your elbows. Finish the movement by squeezing your triceps while maintaining a slight bend in your elbows.\n\n


                                </string>


    <string name="pose21">      Step 1: Attach a rope to a cable stack as high as possible and assume a standing position.\n\n
                                Step 2: Grasp the rope with a neutral grip (palms facing in) and lean forward slightly by hinging at the hips.\n\n
                                Step 3: Initiate the movement by extending the elbows and flexing the triceps.\n\n
                                Step 4: Pull the rope downward until the elbows are almost locked out and then slowly lower under control back to the starting position.\n\n
                                Step 5: Repeat for the desired number of repetitions.\n\n


                                </string>


</resources>